{
    "subject": "resource/Get_Carter",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/Britt_Ekland",
    "human_readable": "Britt Ekland stars in Get Carter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9693341255187988,
            "question": "Which actor starred alongside Britt Ekland in Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7517998218536377,
            "question": "Who starred in the film Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6670257449150085,
            "question": "Is Britt Ekland an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615535616874695,
            "question": "In which film did Britt Ekland play a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6500051021575928,
            "question": "What is the title of the film starring Britt Ekland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5411252975463867,
            "question": "Name a movie featuring Britt Ekland."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5364865660667419,
            "question": "What film is Britt Ekland known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3506295382976532,
            "question": "Who directed the film Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32088997960090637,
            "question": "What genre is the film Get Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2790776491165161,
            "question": "When was the film Get Carter released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Britt Ekland stars in Get Carter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7251_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Get Carter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7251_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Get Carter?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7251_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What film is Britt Ekland known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7251_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_164.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7251_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Britt Ekland starred in the film \"Get Carter\" (1971), which supports the statement that Britt Ekland stars in Get Carter."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}